thedailybanter.com 2017-08-30

# The Daily Banter Privacy Policy - The Daily Banter

The Daily Banter ( **“Company,” “we”** or **“us”** ) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy (the **“Policy”** ) explains how information that directly identifies you ( **“personal information”** ) is collected, used and disclosed by the Company in connection with our website at [TheDailyBanter.com](http://thedailybanter.com/) (the **“Site”** ). The Policy also may describe some of our practices for information that we collect or obtain that does not directly identify you. While this information is not personal information under this Policy, we may choose to treat as personal information in our sole discretion. By visiting or providing information through the Site, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy.

## 1\. Information We Collect, and How We Collect It

We collect information and personal information when you visit or use the Site. This collection includes information that you provide in connection with the Site, information we receive from third parties, and information that is collected automatically such as through the use of cookies and other technologies.

### Information That You Provide

We collect information and personal information that you provide in connection with the Site. The categories of information we collect can include:

  *  **Registration information.** We collect personal information that you provide when you register on a Site, such as for a subscription or membership. If you use a social media or other third party service account to register, this information may include your name, user ID, profile picture, and other profile information that the social media account or third party service shares with us. If you do not use a social media or other third party service account to register, and you register directly with the Site, we may collect information such as your name, username, email address, password, and other information you provide.
  *  **Paid subscriptions and memberships.** If you sign up for a paid subscription or membership, we and/or our service providers may collect your payment information.
  *  **Mailing List Information.** We will collect your email address if you provide it through a Site, such as to receive newsletters, updates, or promotions.
  *  **Inquiries and Feedback.** If you contact us, we will collect the information that you provide us, such as your contact information and the contents of your communication with us.

### Information from Third Parties

We also collect and receive information about you from third parties, including the following:

  *  **Information we receive from social networking sites.** When you interact with the Site through social media websites and services like Facebook, such as when you login to the Site or using your social media credentials, share content from the Site with your social media accounts, use plugins or widgets we may receive information from those websites and services. The information we receive may include your public profile information, profile picture, user name, user ID associated with your social media account, email address, and any other information you permit the social media website or service to share with us or third parties generally. The data we receive may depend upon your privacy settings with the social media website or service, though we do not control those settings or promise they will be effective. You should always review and customize your privacy settings with social media websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Site.
  *  **Information we receive from service providers.** We may receive information about you from service providers who help us with the Site. For example, we may receive information from Say Media, Inc., which helps us to provide the Site and Site functionality, including the ability to sign up for an account at the Site and at other websites that Say Media, Inc. assists with.
  *  **Information we receive from third parties.** We may receive information about you from data brokers and other companies that sell or license data about people. This information may include demographic data (age range, gender, etc.), interests (e.g. shopping categories or topics of interest), ZIP Code or other similar location level data, IP addresses or unique device identifiers, and other information that they make available. We may also collect information about you from public records or that is otherwise publicly available.

### Information That Is Automatically Collected (Cookies and Other Technologies)

We also automatically collect information about you and any computer or device you use to access the Site. Some of the information we collect, and ways we collect it, on the Site include:

  *  **Cookies.** We may send one or more cookies — small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer or device that allows us to uniquely identify your browser, computer, or device. A cookie may also convey other information to us, such as your Internet Protocol ( **“IP”** ) address, unique device identifiers, your browser settings and specifications, and information about how you use the Site (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access it, and other actions you take on it). Cookies also allow us to track your usage of the Site over time.
  *  **Scripts.** We may use scripts — short segments of computer code included in a web page or other content that can be used to set and access a cookie on your computer and to record your activity on a website.
  *  **Log Files.** We may record log file information which may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, unique device identifiers, information about your device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.
  *  **Clear GIFs and Click-Stream Data.** We may employ clear GIFs (also known as web beacons or pixel tags) which may collect information about you, your computer or device such as your web request, IP address, unique device identifiers, browser type, information about your device, pages viewed, and information about cookies, all of which can show your usage patterns for the Site. We also use clear GIFs in conjunction with cookies to collect click-stream data which allows us to understand how visitors move from page to page within websites.
  *  **Mobile Device Information, Identifiers and Location Data.** When you use a mobile device, we may collect and store a unique identifier associated with your device (including, for example, a UDID, Unique ID for Advertisers ( **“IDFA”** ), Google Ad ID, or Windows Advertising ID), mobile carrier, device type, model and manufacturer, mobile device operating system brand and model, phone number, and, depending on your mobile device settings, your geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. A unique identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Company. A unique identifier may convey information to us about how you browse the Site. A unique identifier may remain persistently on your device, and some features of the Site may not function properly if use or availability of unique identifiers or location data are impaired or disabled.

## 2\. Information Third Parties Collect

When you visit the Site third parties may obtain information about you or your computer or device. These third parties may include:

  *  **Service Providers.** We may use service providers to help with the Site or any other lawful activity may do, including the other activities we describe under this Policy. This means service providers may collect, process, and store any of the information that we may collect under the Policy, and information collected in connection with the Site may be collected directly by our service providers. For example, we may use service providers to help us process payments, store information we collect, facilitate interaction with the Site such as in forums or comments, and receive and transmit emails and communications. For example, we may use Say Media, Inc. to help with these and other purposes, including providing this Site and the features and functionality available on the Site.
  *  **Third Party Tracking and Online Advertising.** Third party ad networks, social media companies, and other third party services may collect information about you, your computer or device when you visit or use the Site. This information may be collected automatically, including through cookies, social media plug-ins, and other technologies. The information collected, and manner in which it is collected, may include the information and methods described in the “Information That Is Automatically Collected (Cookies and Other Technologies)” section above. These third parties may collect information about your use of the Site over time, and they may combine it with other information that they possess or obtain about you, such as about your use of other websites and services. These third parties may use this information for our or for third party purposes, including commercial purposes such as tailoring advertising to you on the Site or in other locations like third party websites and services. Some examples of third parties that we use include the following: (1) Google Analytics, which may use technologies like clear GIFs and cookies to collect information, including for our and for Google’s own purposes. Google wants us to provide you with a link to its webpage “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>; (2) DoubleClick, which may use technologies like clear GIFs, cookies, and its Audience Management tags, to collect information, including for our and for DoubleClick and Google’s own purposes. Additional DoubleClick privacy information is available at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>; (3) Say Media, Inc., which may use technologies like clear GIFs and cookies to collect information including for our, its, and third party commercial and advertising purposes. Additional Say Media, Inc. privacy information is available at <http://www.saymedia.com/fine-print>. For information about choices that you may have about this information collection and use, see the “Your Choices” Section below.

## 3\. How We Use Information

We collect, use, process, combine, retain and store information and personal information that we collect or receive for a variety of purposes, including the following:

  * For our business activities, including to operate, maintain, and provide the features and functionality of the Site;
  * To track your preferences, and to maintain your account and subscription;
  * To process your payments (e.g., for subscriptions);
  * To communicate with you and respond to your requests, such as to respond to your questions, contact you about changes to the Site, account-related matters, or other matters related to the Site;
  * To provide you with customized or personalized content or information on the Site;
  * For our and third party marketing and advertising purposes, such as to market to you or offer you our and third party special offers or other products or services we think that you may be interested in;
  * To track analytics and use of the Site;
  * To monitor the effectiveness of our Site features and functionality;
  * To monitor and prevent fraud and abuse, enforce this Policy, to resolve disputes, and otherwise to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights, and to protect our business interests and the interests and rights of third parties;
  * To comply with contractual and legal obligations and requirements;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide personal information; and
  * For any other lawful purpose, or other purpose that you consent to.

## 4\. Sharing of Information

We also transmit, disclose, grant access to, make available, and provide ( **“Disclose”** ) personal information to third parties, including:

  * To service providers, subcontractors, partners, vendors, consultants, and others that help us with any of the purposes noted above or otherwise in this Policy;
  * To our affiliates, parent companies, subsidiaries, and other related companies, all for the purposes noted above or otherwise in this Policy;
  * To third parties for our or third party research, marketing and advertising (including online advertising) purposes;
  * To third parties to respond or comply with, in our sole discretion, a court order, subpoena, law enforcement or other government request (with or without notice to you, in our discretion);
  * To buyers, successors, or others in connection with a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us may be among the assets transferred; 
  * To other third parties with your consent or upon your consent; and
  * To third parties, in our discretion, to: (i) satisfy any applicable law or regulation, (ii) enforce this Policy, including the investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of us, the Site, or third parties.

We also will Disclose information that does not constitute personal information to third parties for the purposes noted above, as well as for other purposes in our sole discretion.

We do not control third parties’ use of information or personal information. If you do not want us to Disclose personal information to third parties, please do not use the Site.

## 5\. Information Access and Correction

If you have registered for an account on the Site, we may provide you with the ability to access, review and change certain personal information by logging into your account and using the features and functionalities available there.

Not all personal information is maintained in a format that you can access or change. If you would like to request access to, or correction or deletion of personal information, you may send your request to us at info@thedailybanter.com. We will review your request, and may require you to provide additional information to identify yourself, but we do not promise that we will be able to satisfy your request. For example, the personal information may already have been relied or acted upon, or disclosed to third parties, and we generally do not take steps (or have the ability to take steps) to undo prior reliance or actions. We also may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement, cause the information to be incorrect, or if doing so would be burdensome in our discretion.

## 6\. Your Choices

We strive to give you choices about how your personal information is collected and used. For example, you can decline to provide certain types personal information to Company or you can stop using the Site, which may limit your use of the Site. We also provide you with the following choices:

  *  **Marketing Emails.** We may send you marketing emails from time to time. If you do not wish to receive them, you can opt-out following the unsubscribe instructions in the emails, or by contacting us at info@thedailybanter.com. We will work to honor your request within 10 business days. If you opt-out, we will still send you emails for service purposes, such as for communications about your account, responses to your requests, and other service purposes. If the emails are sent by third parties, please contact those third parties to opt-out.
  *  **Other Online Advertising.** You may be able to opt-out of other types of online advertising-related cookies used at the Site by actively managing the settings on your browser or mobile device, but we do not promise that such settings will be effective. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for information on the settings offered for cookies or other tracking technologies. You also may be able to opt-out of some online-advertising related cookies: at the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Choice Opt-Out pages at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> and <http://www.aboutads.info/choices-mobile> (for mobile devices); at the Network Advertising Initiative consumer opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>; for Say Media, Inc. by following the instructions at <http://www.saymedia.com/fine-print>; and for Disqus (a third party we may use on the Site for comments) using the options at <https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951>. To learn more about cookies, you may wish to visit <https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0042-cookies-leaving-trail-web>.

## 7\. Do Not Track Preferences

While we want to honor your privacy as described in this Policy, unfortunately the Site does not monitor for or behave differently if your computer or browser transmits a “do not track” or similar message to us or the Site.

## 8\. Data Protection

We take what we believe to be commercially reasonable steps to help protect personal information that we collect, but we do not guarantee that personal information will be completely protected. For example, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Any transmission of personal information by you is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site, including the illegal acts of third parties (such as criminal hacking).

## 9\. Data Retention

We tend to keep personal information for as long as we deem necessary for our business purposes, or as otherwise required to operate the Site, comply with your requests, or comply with applicable law.

## 10\. Information From Children

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13, and believe that your child may have provided us with personal information, please contact us at info@thedailybanter.com, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information.

## 11\. Third Party Websites

The Site may include links to third party websites and online services. This Policy does not describe the privacy practices of those websites or services. Please review the privacy policies of those websites or services before providing personal information to them.

## 12\. Updates to This Policy

We may amend this Policy from time to time. When we do so, we will update the “Last Revision Date” at the end of the Policy. Your continued use of the Site after an updated Policy is posted constitutes your consent to the revised Policy.

## 13\. Governing Law

This Policy is governed by the laws of the State of California and the United States of America.

## 14\. Contacting Us

If have questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at info@thedailybanter.com.

## 15\. Last Revision Date

This Policy was last revised on September 23, 2016.
